<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 15:31:33 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cjyu9211.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is killing &#39;trending topics&#39;</title>
      <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/biz_news_180604/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 15:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/biz_news_180604/</guid>
      <description>Facebook is killing trending topics  본 내용은 wired의 기사 내용을 번역, 요약한 내용임을 미리 밝힙니다. (06.01.18 자 기사); 링크는 본 문서 최하단에 있습니다.  지난 금요일에 올라온 포스트에 따르면, Facebook이 Trending Topics라는 기능을 제거하고 있다고 한다. Trending Topics는 화면의 우측에 있으며, 사용자들이 활발히 토론중인 주제를 보여주는 기능이다. 이 기능은 Facebook Trends API를 포함한 모든 서비스가 다음 주부터 공식적으로 폐기될 예정이다.
Facebook new products의 헤드인 Alex Hardiman은 해당 기능이 예상보다 많이 이용되고 있지 않기에 폐기할 예정이라고 전했다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>구글코리아 Cloud IoT PM 리크루팅</title>
      <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/google_recruit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 13:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/google_recruit/</guid>
      <description>구글코리아 Cloud IoT PM recruit 약 2년 전부터 Intel, Nvidia, Google, FB 등 Tech 회사들의 커리어 사이트에서 alerts를 받고 있다. Engineering 팀 혹은 Product 팀의 공고를 위주로 알림을 받고 있는데, Engineering 혹은 Research 팀의 Job Description(JD)를 통해서는 장기적으로 이 회사가 어떤 기술에 관심을 갖고 있는 지, Product 팀의 JD를 통해서는 단기적으로 이 회사가 현재 보유한 기술 혹은 인력을 통해 어떤 사업을 기획하고 있는 지 간접적으로 확인할 수 있다. 이러한 정보들은 국내 언론 매체를 통해 획득하기 힘들다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 1: NLP with DL</title>
      <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/224n_lecture1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 12:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/224n_lecture1/</guid>
      <description>Lecture 1: NLP with DL 본 카테고리는 Stanford University School of Engineering 에서 공개한 내용인 CS224n- NLP with Deep Learning 강의를 개인 공부하고 요약한 내용이다. 원본은 본문 최하단의 링크를 참조하면 된다.
What is Natural Language Processing (NLP)?  NLP는 1) 전산학, 2) 인공지능, 3) 언어학이 교차하는 부분의 학문이다. NLP는 컴퓨터로 하여금 자연어를 이해하고 처리하는 능력을 배양하는 기술이다. 최근 적용된 사례로는 Apple의 Siri, Google의 Google Assistant, Facebook의 Facebook M을 예로 들 수 있다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 12:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjyu9211.github.io/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Objectives This blog is created to record and share the editor&amp;rsquo;s personal projects and ideas.
The editor majors in electrical engineering at his undergraduate and studied fundamental subjects in semiconductors, signal processing, computer architecture, and integrated circuits. During his undergraduate, he conducted an independent research on deep learning also.
He is interested in commercializing high technology both in electrical engineering and computer science. For more information about the author, please refer to About.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjyu9211.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Chanjong Yu is an incoming Associate Consultant at Bain &amp;amp; Company, Seoul. As an Electrical Engineering undergraduate at Korea University, he has raised interest in a wide range of electrical engineering and computer science.
He worked for about 2.5 years as an RF engineer at SOLiD Technology, inc, and as an undergraduate researcher at Mirae Asset A.I. Fintech Research Center and Complex Data Analytics Laboratory for about a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://cjyu9211.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjyu9211.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> First Name  Last Name  E-Mail  City  State AL CA IL      Send   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>